A Finding Aid to the Jimmy Hedges Papers and Rising Fawn Folk Art Gallery Records, 1969-2016, bulk 1991-2013, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
Jimmy Hedges papers and Rising Fawn Folk Art Gallery records
1969-2016, bulk 1991-2013
Archives of American Art
Hedges, Jimmy, 1942-2014
AAA.hedgjimm
Archival Resource Key
23.5 Linear feet
15.63 Gigabytes
The papers of art collector and dealer Jimmy Hedges and the records of his Rising Fawn Folk Art Gallery measure 23.5 linear feet and 15.63 GB and date from 1969-2016, with the bulk of the material dating from 1991-2013. The collection documents Hedges's career as a dealer of outsider art and as an advocate for self-taught artists. Records include administrative and sales records, correspondence, artist files, collector and gallery files, exhibition and art fair files, regional files, printed and digital material, photographic material, and unidentified sound and video recordings. The bulk of the collection consists of artist files and color photographs documenting hundreds of artists that Hedges visited at their homes and studios, including Georgia Blizzard, Howard Finster, Homer Green, Bessie Harvey, Danny Hoskinson, Paul Lancaster, A.J. Mohammed, Charlie Simmons, Jimmy Lee Sudduth, Mose Tolliver, and Purvis Young, among many others.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged as 9 series.
Missing Title
Series 1: Administrative and Sales Records, 1969-1971, 1991-2015 (Boxes 1-4; 3.9 linear feet, ER01-ER03; 0.134 GB)
Series 2: Correspondence, 1974, 1981, 1990-2013 (Boxes 4-5; 0.2 linear feet)
Series 3: Artist Files, 1985-2014 (Boxes 5-9, 31, 33, OV 32; 4.6 linear feet, ER04-ER15; 5.35 GB)
Series 4: Collector and Gallery Files, 1992-2014 (Boxes 9-10; 1.2 linear feet)
Series 5: Exhibition and Art Fair Records, circa 1992-2013 (Boxes 10-11; 1.3 linear feet, ER16-ER18; 1.52 GB)
Series 6: Regional Files, 1976, 1980s-2012 (Boxes 11-13; 1.7 linear feet)
Series 7: Printed Material, 1980-2013 (Boxes 13-16, OV 32; 2.2 linear feet, ER19; 0.833 GB)
Series 8: Photographic Material, circa 1990-2011 (Boxes 16-30, 34-35; 7.9 linear feet, ER20-ER35; 7.79 GB)
Series 9: Unidentified Sound and Video Recordings, undated (Boxes 30-31; 0.5 linear feet)
Conditions Governing Access
Use of original papers requires an appointment. Use of archival audiovisual records or born digital records with no duplicate access copy requires advance notice.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated 2016 by James R. Hedges IV on behalf of the Hedges Descendants Trust and in 2018 by James R. Hedges IV on behalf of Wildcat Asset Managment, LLC.
Scope and Contents
The records of art collector and dealer Jimmy Hedges and his Rising Fawn Folk Art Gallery measure 23.5 linear feet and 15.63 GB and date from 1969-2016, with the bulk of the material dating from 1991-2013. The collection documents Hedges's career as a dealer of outsider art and as an advocate for self-taught artists. Records include administrative and sales records, correspondence, artist files, collector and gallery files, exhibition and art fair files, regional files, printed and digital material, photographic material, and unidentified sound and video recordings. The bulk of the collection consists of artist files and color photographs documenting hundreds of artists that Hedges visited at their homes and studios, including Georgia Blizzard, Howard Finster, Homer Green, Bessie Harvey, Danny Hoskinson, Paul Lancaster, A.J. Mohammed, Charlie Simmons, Jimmy Lee Sudduth, Mose Tolliver, and Purvis Young, among many others.
Biographical / Historical
James R. "Jimmy" Hedges III (1942-2014), was an artist, art collector and dealer of Outsider Art and Folk art in Tennessee and Georgia. Hedges established the Rising Fawn Folk Art Gallery, Lookout Mountain, Georgia.
Born into a prominent family from Chattanooga, Jimmy Hedges was a lifelong philanthropist as a trustee of his family's Tonya Memorial Foundation. His true vocation, however, was as an artist, collector, and dealer of outsider art and as an advocate for self-taught artists. Hedges discovered his love of wood carving as a teenager, when he created song birds, and returned to making art at age forty. Using a chain saw, he carved sculptures of Southerners he had encountered in his travels, including artists. His colleagues in this sector of the fine art craft world were predominantly southern African American self-taught painters, sculptors, potters, and carvers. Befriending them and collecting their work led Hedges to establish Rising Fawn Folk Art Gallery in 1993, building a gallery space in the early 2000s on his 500-acre farm in Lookout Mountain, Georgia.
An unconventional art dealer, Hedges would hand-deliver work to collectors' homes, driving his truck through backroads and stopping along the way to visit with artists and purchase more works to sell. He was an active presence at the Outsider Art Fair and self-taught artist exhibitions throughout the U.S., as well as at Slotin Folk Art auctions and prison auctions. His aim was to improve the economic condition of fellow artists and raise their profiles among curators and critics. Hedges' development of an archive was essential to this goal.
Self-taught artists; Art -- Collectors and collecting; Photographs; Art dealers -- Tennessee; Sound recordings; Video recordings; Folk art; Outsider art; Artists' studios -- Photographs; Lancaster, Paul; Blizzard, Georgia, 1919-2002; Mohammed, A.J.; Green, Homer, 1910-2002; Simmons, Charlie; Hoskinson, Danny; Harvey, Bessie, 1929-; Sudduth, Jimmy Lee, 1910-2007; Rising Fawn Folk Art Gallery; Tolliver, Mose, 1920-; Finster, Howard, 1916-2001; Young, Purvis, 1943-
- Administrative and Sales Records, 1991-2015; 1969-1971; Series 1; Archival Resource Key; 3.9 Linear feet Boxes 1-4; 0.134 Gigabytes ER01-ER03
  Scope and Contents
  Administrative and sales records include Hedges's numerous address books, mailing lists, and client information, as wells as art appraisals, auction records, and art inventory lists. Documentation on the Rising Fawn Folk Art Gallery at Lookout Mountain include records of the gallery construction, gallery scrapbook, sculpture garden records, digital records, and postcard designs. Also found here are extensive gallery sales records, including sales books which record each transaction with the date, name of purchaser, description of artwork, and sales price. Many of these sales books were used to document sales at regional art fairs and events. Additional sales records include print-outs of online eBay transactions. Researchers should note that additional sales records can be found within the Artist Files, Collector and Gallery Files, Exhibition and Art Fair Records, and Regional Files.
  - Address Book, "Crafts", undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Address Book, "Kentucky, Virginia, and Up East", undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Address Book, Regional, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Address Book, Regional, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Address Book, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Address Book, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Address Book, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Address Book, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Address Book, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Address Book, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Accounts Receivable, 1995-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - American Visionary Art Museum, 1994-2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 4-5)
  - Appointment Books, 2014-2015; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 6-7)
  - Art Appraisal, 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Art Associations, 1996; 2007-2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Art Loop Trail, circa 2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Artprice.com, 2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Art Purchased, 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Artwork Lists, circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Auction Lists, Slotin Folk Art, 2007-2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Auction Tags and Labels, circa 2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Sally Brooks, 1991-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Client Notebook, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Conferences, Folk Art Society of America, 1992-2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 18-19)
  - Early Art Purchases, 1969-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - EBay Transactions, 2003-2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 21-26)
  - EBay Transactions, 2010-2011; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 1-2)
  - E-mail Addresses Notebook, circa 2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Folklorists, 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Gallery Construction, circa 2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Gallery Inventory and Price Lists, circa 2006-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Gallery Inventory, Digital Document, 2007; Archival Resource Key; 0.001 Gigabytes One computer file (Folder ER01)
  - Gallery Scrapbook, 1991-2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 7-9)
  - Invoices, "Visions of America", 1991-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 10-11)
  - Kimball M. Sterling, Inc., circa 1996-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 12-14)
  - Mailing Lists, Business Cards, and Loose Addresses, circa 1990s-2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 15-16)
  - Mailing Lists and Business Card Proofs, Digital Documents, 2004-2010; Archival Resource Key; 0.001 Gigabytes 14 computer files (Folder ER02)
  - Museum of American Folk Art (The Clarion), 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Nancy Ward Statue, 2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Notebook, circa 2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Notes, 1992-2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Photography, Sharon Hudson, circa 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Postcard Orders, 1995-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 22-23)
  - Private Collections Appraisals, circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Receipts from Artists, 1991-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Robert S. Brunk Auction Services, Inc., 2008; 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Sales Book, 2010; 2002-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Sales Book, 2003-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Sales Book, Outsider Art Fair, 2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Sales Book, Shows, 2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Sales Book, 2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Sales Book, 2006-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Sales Books, 2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 2-3)
  - Sales Book, 2007-2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Sales Books, 2008-2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 5-6)
  - Sales Book, 2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Sales Books, 2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 8-9)
  - Sales Book, 2010-2011; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Sales Book, 2010-2013; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Sales Book, Laurel Lake Cabin, 2011; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Sales Book, 2011-2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Sales Book, 2011-2013; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Sales Book, 2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Sales and Purchase Records, Miscellaneous, 1990s-2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Sculpture Garden and Brochure, circa 2006-2009; Archival Resource Key; Includes born-digital records, see ER03 (Box 4, Folder 17-19)
  - Sculpture Garden Brochure and Photographs, Digital Photographs and Documents, 2009; Archival Resource Key; 0.132 Gigabytes 55 computer files (Folder ER03)
  - Sisters in Clay, 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - T-Shirts, 1991-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 21-22)
  - Unidentified Draft Manuscript, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Water Leak, 2011-2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Correspondence, 1990-2013; 1981; 1974; Series 2; Archival Resource Key; 0.2 Linear feet Boxes 4-5
  Correspondence is scattered and includes greeting cards, postcards, and letters received by Hedges from artists and collectors, as well as a small amount of incoming and outgoing gallery business correspondence with arts organizations, galleries, and others. Researchers should note that most of Hedges's correspondence can be found within the other series in this collection.
  - Correspondence, 1974; 1981; 1990-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, 1993-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, 2000-2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 2010-2013; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Artist Files, 1985-2016; Series 3; Archival Resource Key; 4.6 Linear feet Boxes 5-9, 31, 33, OV 32; 5.35 Gigabytes ER04-ER15
  Found here are nearly 200 files containing Hedges's documentation on outsider, folk, and self-taught artists. Files may contain artist fact sheets written by Hedges, postcards, brochures, correspondence, photographs, and purchase and sales records. Research material on artists include newspaper and magazine clippings, photocopies of publications, and exhibition catalogs. A few files also include digital photographs and recordings. One videocassette is included in the file on Herbert Hemphill and one sound cassette is included in the file on Howard Finster. Also found are three folders containing research material on quilters and the Southern quilting tradition. Researchers should note that Hedges's extensive collection of photographs of artists and their artwork is included in Series 8: Photographic Material. The 2018 addition contains further material on Purvis Young.
  Arrangement
  Files are arranged alphabetically by name of artist, followed by files containing single fact sheets on miscellaneous artists in alphabetical order.
  - Minnie and Garland Adkins, circa 1993-2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Leroy Almon, circa 1991-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Wayne Anderson, 2011-2012; Archival Resource Key; Includes born-digital records, see ER04 (Box 5, Folder 6-7)
  - Wayne Anderson, Digital Photographs, 2012; Archival Resource Key; 0.018 Gigabytes 14 computer files (Folder ER04)
  - Eddie Arning, circa 2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Jessie Aron, circa 2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Herbert Baggett, circa 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Jace Barnett, 2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Nathaniel Barrow, 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Leonard "Stickman" Belcher, circa 1992-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Hector Alonzo Benavides, circa 2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Mozell Benson, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Ned Berry, circa 2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Georgia Blizzard, 1994-2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Carl Block, 2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Wess Bobo, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Hawkins Boldin, circa 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Frank "Preacher" Boyle, circa 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Alan Wayne "Haint" Bradley, 1999-2013; Archival Resource Key; Includes born-digital records, see ER05-ER06 (Box 5, Folder 22-24)
  - Alan Wayne "Haint" Bradley, Artwork, Digital Photographs, 2009; Archival Resource Key; 0.049 Gigabytes 12 computer files (Folder ER05)
  - Alan Wayne "Haint" Bradley, Artwork, Digital Video Recordings, 2009; Archival Resource Key; 0.344 Gigabytes Five computer files (Folder ER06)
    Works described in videos: Family of Circles Having Fun; Tubular Stationary Rotary Mechanism; Behind Granpaw's Toolshed; Odyssey Merging with the Flow; and, Vanilla Blue.
  - Fred Bradford, circa 2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Jerry Brown, 1989-2013; Archival Resource Key; Includes one videocassette (VHS). (Box 5, Folder 26-27)
  - Katherine "Panky" Brown, "Panky's Pantry Secrets Revisited", Digital Photographs and Documents, 2004; Archival Resource Key; 0.004 Gigabytes 23 computer files (Folder ER07)
  - Richard Burnside, circa 2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Vernon Burwell, circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Shane Campbell, circa 2009-2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Y. G. Casey, circa 2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Henry Ray Clark, circa 1989-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 32-33)
  - Raymond Coins, circa 1989-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Jerry Coker, circa 2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Jim Collins, circa 1990s-2007; Archival Resource Key; Includes born-digital records, see ER08-ER09 (Box 6, Folder 2-3)
  - Irish Odyssey, Interactive Digital Presentation, 2004; Archival Resource Key; 0.042 Gigabytes One computer file Click on Slideshow-Player.exe to render presentation. (Folder ER08)
  - Volumes, Digital Presentation, 2001; Archival Resource Key; 0.036 Gigabytes One computer file (Folder ER09)
  - Charles Counts, circa 2000-2011; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 4-5)
  - Burlon Craig, 2002-2011; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - William Cross, 2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Harrold Crowell, circa 2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - John Culver, 2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - David Dorman, 2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Patrick Davis, circa 2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Alva Gene Dexhimer, 1997; 2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Thornton "Buck" Dial, circa 1990s-2011; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Burgess Dulaney, circa 1990s-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Roger Dorset, circa 2009; Archival Resource Key; Includes born-digital records, see ER10 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - And That's What Happened, Digital Video Recording, 2009; Archival Resource Key; 0.909 Gigabytes Two computer files (Folder ER10)
  - Brian Dowdall, circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Gerald "Creative" DePrie, circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - William Edmonson, circa 1988-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Minnie Evans, circa 2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Nora Ezell, 1991-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 20-21)
  - Howard Finster, circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 sound cassette. (Box 6, Folder 22-23)
    Oversized material housed in OV 32.
  - Walter Fleming, circa 2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Sybil Gibson, circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Lee Godie, circa 2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Lewis Gravitt, circa 2011; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Homer Green, circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Joseph Charles Hardin, circa 2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Otesia Harper, circa 1990s-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Alyne Harris, circa 2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Bessie Harvey, 1990s-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - All the Way to the Worldle, Digital Video Recording, 2006; Archival Resource Key; 0.685 Gigabytes Three computer files (Folder ER11)
  - Herbert Waide Hemphill Jr., 1989; Archival Resource Key; 1 Videocassettes (VHS) (Box 31, Folder 1)
    "Studios at the Lakes - A Tribute to Herbert Waide Hemphill Jr."
  - Mark Hewitt, 2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - B. R. Hilton, circa 2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Lonnie Holley, 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 36)
    Oversized item housed in OV 32.
  - Danny Hoskinson, 1996-2010; Archival Resource Key; Includes born-digital materials, see ER12 (Box 6, Folder 37-40)
  - Danny Hoskinson, Digital Photographs, 2008; Archival Resource Key; 0.024 Gigabytes Nine computer files (Folder ER12)
  - Stephanie Howard, 2013; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Robert Howell, circa 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - L. V. Hull, circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Clementine Hunter, 1993; circa 2010-2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Mark Issenberg, circa 2001; 2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Alvin Jarrett, circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - James Harold Jennings, 2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Anderson Johnson, circa 2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Daniel Johnson, circa 2006; 2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Mama Johnson, circa 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - S. L. Jones, circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Gertrude Kasday, 2003; 1985; Archival Resource Key; Includes born-digital materials, see ER13 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Gertrude Kasday, Digital Photographs, 2003; Archival Resource Key; 0.063 Gigabytes 14 computer files (Folder ER13)
  - Rosemary Kocsy, circa 1995-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - George Kornegay, circa 1990s-2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - George Lafone, circa 2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Paul Lancaster, circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 9-10)
  - Billy Lemming, circa 1989-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Joe Lewis Light, 1993-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Woodie Long, 1985-2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Charlie Lucas, 1996-2011; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Makiki, circa 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Rebecca Marshall, 2006-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Mbuti (Pygmy) Women, circa 2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Wayne D. "Mad Mac" McCaffrey, circa 2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Echo McCallister, circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Justin McCarthy, circa 2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Carl McKenzie, 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Mario Mesa, circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - R. A. Miller, 2006-2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Sister Gertrude Morgan, circa 2008-2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - A. J. Muhammed, circa 1992-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Karen Reinert, circa 2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Royal Robertson, circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Simone Robinson, circa 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Juanita Rogers, circa 2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Marie Rogers, circa 2003-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Sulton Rogers, 1992-2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Max Romain, circa 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Cher Shaffer, 2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Steve Shepard, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Charles Simmons, 1994-2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 35-36)
  - Kevin Simmons, 1997-2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Bernice Sims, circa 2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 38)